# Shubham Mishra

A self-motivated graduate with skills of a Full-Stack developer with 3 years of experience and my main strength is logical and algorithm thinking. I worked on JavaScript, NodeJS and ReactJS projects. I like new technologies and upgrading my knowledge and skills.

## **EXPERIENCE**

# Infosys Ltd. Bengaluru — Specialist Programmer

Dec 2022 - Present

Working as a full-stack software developer.

- Created the RESTful API endpoint and UI of the insurance domain projects.
- Integrated and managed databases such as MongoDB or MySQL to store and retrieve data efficiently, ensuring data consistency and integrity.
- Created various functionalities like Validation, Filter, Feature, rider premium, product premium --etc.
- Created unit test and postman collection to test the API.
- Tools & Technology: Javascript, NodeJS, ReactJS, MongoDB, SQL, Git.

# **Coradius Technologies Pvt. Ltd. Mumbai** — *Junior Programmer*

MAY 2021 - DEC 2022.

Worked as a full-stack software developer in Insurance domain projects.

- Developed new product's RESTful API and UI from scratch including requirement analysis, development, and Collaboration with Teams for designing request and response structure.
- Integrated various product and managed databases such as MongoDB and MySQL to store and retrieve data.
- Created unit test and postman collection for all products.
- Developed script for measuring performance using Autocannon.
- Tools & Technology: Javascript, SQL, NodeJS,ReactJS, Git, MongoDB, Mocha, Chai.

# **PROJECTS**

- ❖ Aditya Birla Health Insurance
  - > Active Assure Diamond
  - > Active Health Platinum Essential
  - > Active Health Platinum Enhanced
- Annuity Insurance
  - > Birla Guaranteed Annuity Plus
  - > HDFC Pension Guaranteed Annuity Plan
  - > TATA Smart Annuity Plan
- Life Insurance
  - > HDFC Click 2 Protect Life

### **EDUCATION**

# Kamla Nehru Institute Of Technology, Sultanpur— B.Tech

AUGUST 2016 - OCTOBER 2020

I completed my engineering in Electronics Engineering securing 70.30%.

#### sm863037@gmail.com

9120596086

LinkedIn:https://www.linkedin.com/in/shubha m-mishra-83a8401bb/

GitHub:<u>https://www.linkedin.com/in/shubha</u> m-mishra-83a8401bb/

#### **SKILLS**

#### **Technical Skills:**

Data Structure and Algorithm
Object-Oriented Programming
Web Development

Web Development

Competitive Programming

# Programming Language:

C++, Javascript.

## Frontend:

HTML5, CSS3, React js, Redux.

#### Backend:

Nodejs(Express).

## DATABASE:

MySQL, MongoDB.

# **TRAINING and COURSES**

# Web development-MNNIT Prayagraj

I have completed this 1-month training at MNNIT, Prayagraj.

#### Algorithm Toolbox -Coursera

I have completed this 2-month duration Course.

#### Data Structure -Coursera

I have completed this 4-week duration course.

# Web Development Course-Udemy

I have completed this 30 hrs Course.

#### **CERTIFICATE AND AWARDS**

Spot Award - May 2022 Certificate of Participation - Geeks Lab, ReactIs

### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Solved Competitive Programming Questions on Leetcode and Spoj.

Qualifier of Codechef Snackdown 2019 Qualifier Round.